alright guys welcome back in this tutorial I want to talk to you about
好的家伙欢迎回来 教程 我想和你谈谈
something called threading so first of all let's go ahead and understand what a
首先称为线程的东西 所有让我们继续前进，了解什么是
thread is and why they're useful so up to now we've been building some very
线程是为什么它们 如此 有用 到目前为止我们已经建立了一些非常好的
simple programs and you learn that pretty much building a program is kind
简单的程序，你了解到 几乎建立一个 程序是善良的
of like giving your computer ACEF instructions we need to give it a nice
喜欢给你的电脑ACEF 说明我们需要给 它一个好的
logical order to follow follow step 1 then 2 then 3 that's pretty much what
按照 逻辑顺序 执行步骤 1 然后2然后3那几乎是什么
writing code is all about giving your computer some instructions to follow now
编写代码就是为了给你 计算机现在要遵循一些指示
sometimes it's useful to break up a single program and have it do multiple things at a time now I want warn you
有时分手是有用的 单个程序，让它做多个 现在我想要 警告你的 事情
guys most of the time this isn't a good idea because like whenever you're making
大多数时候，这不是一个好人 想法， 因为 喜欢无论何时 你正在 制作
a calculation you just can't like add the numbers or divide them or do
你不能添加的计算 数字或划分他们或做
whatever you want in any order outs your going to get a bad result you need to
你想以任何顺序 出局无论你 你需要 得到 一个糟糕的结果
follow a specific order so most of the time you don't want to use threads in
按照特定的顺序，从而大部分 时间你不想使用线程
your program is going to run fine so when would building a program that does
你的程序将运行精 做 什么时候建立一个 程序
multiple things at once be beneficial well one of the most common examples
多事情 一次 是有益的 这是最常见的 例子之一
whenever I teach threads is whenever you're making a messenger program what
每当我教线程时，无论什么时候 你正在制作一个信使程序
you're going to do is you're basically going to build two different programs
你要做的就是你基本上 打算建立两个不同的程序
that run at a time one of them is going to be responsible for sending messages
同时他们中的一个 运行 是 怎么回事 负责 发送消息
and one of them is going to be responsible for listening for messages
其中之一 将 是 负责收听 消息
so whenever you're talking with someone like instant messenger it doesn't matter
所以，每当你 和某人说话时 像即时通讯一样无所谓
when they send the message or excuse me when you send your message or when you
当他们发送消息或原谅 我 当您发送消息或何时发送消息
receive a message um you know you don't have to like wait for them to send a
收到一条消息， 你知道你没有 不得不等待 他们 发送一个
message before you can start typing so what you would want to do is you would
您可以开始输入之前的消息 你会想做什么
want to build two different objects and one is responsible for sending out and
想要建立两个不同的对象和 一个负责发送和
one is responsible for receiving or listening and it builds a really cool
一个人负责 接收或 听，它 真的很酷
like a chat or Skype or instant messenger application so let me go ahead and show you guys how to do that right
喜欢聊天， Skype或 即时消息 信使应用所以让我继续吧 并告诉你们如何做到 这一点
now so the first thing we need to do is import threading and what this does is
所以 现在 我们需要 做 的第一 件事 就是 导入线程以及它的作用
it a class that what we're going to do is
它 我们要做的一个课程
we're going to make anything like a Bucky's messenger and what we're going
我们要制作 类似的东西 Bucky的使者和我们要去的东西
to do is we're actually going to inherit from this class so remember anything you
要做的是我们 真的要 继承 从这堂课那么记住你
put in here is the parent class that you inherit from so now any object that we
放在这里是你的父类 现在继承我们的任何对象
create that's Bucky's messenger we get a bunch
创建 这是Bucky的使者，我们得到了一堆
of cool built in thread functions so the one function that we need to have is def run now you see it automatically popped
很酷的内置线程函数所以 我们需要的一个功能是def 现在运行你会看到它自动弹出
up because this isn't just a you know a name that I'm picking it off the top of
因为这 不仅仅是你所知道 的 我正在挑选它的名字
my head this is a very specific name that we need to have just kind of
我的 脑袋 这是一个非常具体的名字 我们需要有正中下怀
special to threads so means something special to threads basically whenever we
特殊的线程所以意味着什么 特别是线程基本上每当我们
create a thread it's going to call this run function so it won't off so now
创建一个 它将调用它的 线程 运行功能所以它现在不会关闭
let's go ahead and just write some code in it so just for a simple demonstration
让我们继续，然后写一些代码 在它只是为了一个简单的演示
I mean typically what you'd want to do is make a complex program responsible
我的意思是你通常想做 什么 是一个复杂的程序 负责
for like sending messages every I don't know like you can do it like once a second maybe but for now I'm just going
我不喜欢发送消息 知道 像你可以像 一次 第二个也许， 但现在我 只是去
to loop something ten times to show you guys it's a really good demonstration of
循环 一下十次给你看 伙计们，这是一个很好的演示
how exactly this thread is going to work so for actually I don't even know if I
这个线程究竟是如何运作的 所以其实我甚至不知道 我是否
taught you guys this so you know before whenever I was making a for loop and I
教你这个，所以你以前知道 每当我做一个for循环和我
put like 4x and arrange 10 or fortuna' in range 10
像4x 并 安排 10或 fortuna' 在范围10
well that tuna or X variable is equal to the numbers 1 2 3 4 all the way up the
以及金枪鱼或X变量等于 数1 2 3 4 一路 向上
well it's either 9 or 10 whatever many times you want to loop so you can use
无论 多少，它都是9 或10 你想要循环的时间，以便你 可以使用
that variable and print it out or use it in the calculation or something but
该变量并打印出来或使用它 在计算或东西但
sometimes we just want to loop 10 times and we really don't care what number
有时我们 只想循环10次 我们真的 不在乎什么 号码
we're on or that variable at all so what you can do when you don't really want to
我们在那个或那个变量都是如此 当你不想要时，你可以做到
use that variable or that value you can just put an underscore right there and
使用 那个变量或那个值你可以 只是在那里放下一个下划线
that's the kind of convention it pretty much is saying okay I want to loop 10
这就是那种常规 很多是说好的 我想循环10
times don't really care about the variable so I'm just going to use
时代 并不真正关心 变量所以我只是想用
underscore in place so that's what that means you know just
强调到位 所以这是什么意思，你 只 知道
kind of Python convention so what do I wanted to do ten times well the cool
那种Python约定所以我该怎么做 想做好十次好酷
thing whenever we inherited a bunch of stuff from this thread class or
什么时候我们继承了一堆 从这个线程类的东西或
threating is actually let me type it out because it's kind of current thread part
威胁实际上让我输入它 因为它是当前线程的一部分
we should move my cursor out of the way get name now what we can do is one of
我们应该将我的光标 的方式进行 现在得到我们能做的就是其中之一
the built-in things is we can give every thread a name so it's one of the default
我们可以给每一个内置的东西 线程名称， 因此它是默认名称之一
properties with a thread so all I want to do is I'm going to make two different
带有线程的属性所以我想要的 要做的是我 要做两个不同的事情
threads with two different names and I'm just going to print out their name
有两个不同 名字的线程， 我 只是要打印 出他们的名字
however it X really cool it's not just like printing something out on the
然而它真的很酷，它不仅仅是 喜欢打印出来 的 东西
screen ten times so I'll show you guys how cool it is right now so for our
屏幕十次，所以我会告诉你们 它是 如何 的酷现在 这样对 我们的
messenger this is all we have that's all we need what we did is we now
信使这就是我们所拥有的一切 这就是我们现在所需要的一切
have this class right here but it can be threaded and what this means is you can
这个班级就在这里，但它可以 线程 ，这意味着 你可以
have multiple objects from this class running at the same exact time you don't
有这个类的多个对象 在你没有的同一时间运行
need to wait for one to get done to start the next one so let's go ahead and
需要等待一个 完成 开始下一个，让我们 继续吧
actually create one so I named one X and this is just going to be equal to
实际创建一个，所以我 命名 一个X和 这 只是将是等于
Bucky's messenger and remember one of the built-in properties or the default
Bucky的使者，记得其中一个 内置属性或默认值
properties for a thread is we can give it a name so I'm going to set this name
我们可以给出一个线程的属性 它是一个名字， 所以我要 设置这个名字
equal to and this is just an example send out messages so we'll say that this is what this thread would be responsible
等于，这只是一个例子 发出消息所以我们会说这个 是这个线程负责的
for so now let me go ahead and make another run real quick and in real life
那么现在就让我继续前进， 使 另一个真正的快速和现实生活
what this would be is instead of just giving it a name you would actually you
这将是什么 而 不仅仅是 给它一个名字 你实际上就是你
know add functionality to like receive messages so now we have two threads
知道添加功能 以喜欢接收 消息，所以现在我们有两个线程
right there and check this out right now you're looking at this and said okay there's only one function in here called
就在那里，现在就检查一下 你看着这个，说好的 这里只有一个函数叫做
run so you're probably going to do something like X
跑，所以你可能会这样做 像 X这样的东西
run but that's not the case whenever you create a thread what you want to do is
跑，但不是你的情况 创建一个你想要做的线程
you want to call the start function on that thread so X star and Y start and
要在调用start功能 那个线程让X 星和Y开始了
even though that this is kind of I don't know it doesn't really make sense at
尽管这有点我不喜欢 知道它 真的没有 意义
first whenever you call this start function what it does is it goes to that
每当你打电话给这个开始时 功能它的作用是不言而喻 的是
class and it looks for a function called run so it's it's kind of weird but
class，它查找一个名为的函数 这样运行它 有点奇怪但是
that's how it works so start kicks off a thread now how is
这是它的工作原理 所以现在开始如何开始一个线程
this different than any normal function well check this out actually you can
这与任何正常功能都不同 实际上你 可以看看这个
kind of see here but let me run it one more time just a there we go that's a
有点看到这里， 但让我运行一个 更多的时间只是我们去那里是一个
better example so before whenever we created objects what happened is our
更好的例子，所以在我们之前 创建对象发生的事情是我们的
programs run from top to bottom so it ran this line it finished and then it
程序从上到下运行所以它 跑了这条线完了然后它
went on this line it finished went on the list line and what this line does is
继续这条线完成了继续 列表 行以及此行的作用
is is it creates a thread with the name send out messages and it loops through
是它创建一个名称的线程 发出消息然后循环播放
it ten times so before what happened is this would print send out messages ten
它 的十倍那么之前所发生的事情是 这将打印发送消息十
times and it once it was finished it would move on to the next line but check
时间和它一旦完成它 将 移动到 下一行 ，但检查
this out send send send receive send receive send receive why are they all jumbled together well that's a cool
这个发送发送发送接收发送 收到发送接收 为什么都是 混杂在一起这很酷
thing about threads with threads you don't need to wait for this to finish
关于线程 与线程的事情 不需要等待这个 完成
before moving on to the next line with threads what your program is going to do
在移动到 下一行与 前 线程你的程序将 要做什么
is this is going to say ok this is a thread and I'm going to start it off in
这是否 可以说 这是一个 线程，我要开始吧
other words I'm going to call run and as soon as I'm done before this is even
换句话说，我打算称之为run和as 我很快就完成了
done I'm just going to go on to the next line and do whatever it tells me to sew
做我只是要去 下一个 行， 并做任何它 告诉我缝
again eventually what we have for a brief period of time is both of these
最终 我们拥有了什么 短暂的 时间 就是这些
things running at the exact same time so now our computer program is well a lot
事情在精确的同一时间 运行 ，所以 现在我们的计算机程序很多
more powerful and a lot more faster or a lot faster however the heck you say it so that is how in one
更强大， 更快或更快 不过你说的那么快 这就是一体的
instance you would utilize threads to make a messenger program and again just warning you guys you don't want to use
你会利用线程的实例 再做一个信使程序 警告你们， 你们不想使用它们
threads with everything even though it speeds up your program this would be
即使它 ， 所有线程 这会加速你的程序
really awful in the calculation so say you're like averaging a bunch of numbers
在计算中 真的太糟糕 了 你喜欢平均一堆数字
well you need to add all those numbers together before you do your division so
那么你需要添加所有这些数字 你做你的分裂之前在一起，
if you're like okay add and try to divide at the same time you're going to get one you know
如果你喜欢加入并尝试 在划分你要同时 得到一个你知道的
messed up answer so you wouldn't want to do it in that case scenario but for
搞砸了答案，所以你不会想 在那种情况下这样做，但是
programs that really don't depend on something else to happen and can run
真正不依赖的程序 其他事情发生 ，可以运行
concurrently or at the same time threads are an awesome feature to have so for
同时或同时线程 这是一个很棒的功能
now thank you guys for watching don't forget to subscribe and well I'll see
现在谢谢 你们观看不要 忘 了订阅，我会看到
you later
你以后